<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dr._Prithvi</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Tab 3</string>
    <string name="Tomato"> <b>APPLE SCAB</b>
\n TOMATO EARLY BLIGHT
LEAVES:
Initially small dark spots form on older foliage near the ground
Leaf spots are round, brown and can grow up to half inch in diameter.
Larger spots have target like concentric rings and tissue around spots often turns yellow
Severely infected leaves turn brown and fall off, or dead, dried leaves may cling to the stem
FRUIT:
Fruit can be infected at any stage of maturity
Fruit spots are leathery, black, with raised concentric ridges and generally occur near the stem
Infected fruit may drop from the plant
</string>

    <string name="Apple"> APPLE SCAB

    Symptoms on fruit are similar to those found on leaves.
    Scabby spots are sunken and tan and may have velvety spores in the center.
    As these spots mature, they become larger and turn brown and corky.
    Infected fruit becomes distorted and may crack allowing entry of secondary organism.
</string>

    <string name="Blueberry"> Alternaria Leaf Spot of Blueberry
Alternaria Leaf Spot (Alternaria tenuissima) occurs primarily in the spring during prolonged periods of cool wet weather, when spores are produced in abundance. Leaf symptoms appear as circular to irregular-shaped brown to gray lesions surrounded by a red border. Prolonged periods of high humidity favor disease development.
Bacterial Leaf Scorch of Blueberry
The bacterium Xylella fastidiosa is the causal agent of bacterial leaf scorch of blueberry, which primarily affects cultivars of southern highbush blueberries(interspecific hybrids of Vaccinium corymbosum).
Symptoms on southern highbush blueberries include: marginal scorching of the leaves, premature leaf drop, yellowing of stems and eventual death of the plants.
Double Spot and Gloeocercospora Leaf Spot
In late summer, the double spot fungus develops a secondary necrotic area around the original lesion spreading in an irregular to fan-shaped pattern. The gloeocercospora leaf spot appears on the foliage by mid-summer as large dark brown, circular to angular lesions surrounded by a dark border.
Leaf Rust of Blueberry
•	The disease first appears as yellow leaf spots on the upper leaf surface of new blueberry leaves.
•	Spots later turn reddish brown. Entire leaves may turn brown, die and drop prematurely if infections are severe.
•	Yellowish orange pustules become visible on the lower leaf surface about mid-summer. This disease also occurs sporadically on highbush blueberries after harvest.

</string>
</resources>
